{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Gutter Cleaning Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40072/":{"taskOID":40072,"originalTaskOID":40072,"setID":394,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1554,"questionDisplayText":"Why Gutters Need Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need to have your gutters cleaned?  (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6871,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water isn't draining from the downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Water isn't draining from the downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6887,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water overflows from gutter and drips from joints","answerDisplayText":"Water overflows from gutter and drips from joints","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2896,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters are clogged with leaves and needles","answerDisplayText":"Gutters are clogged with leaves and needles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gutters are clogged with gravel from the roof","answerDisplayText":"Gutters are clogged with gravel from the roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":853,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"As regular maintenance to keep them working properly","answerDisplayText":"As regular maintenance to keep them working properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":947,"questionDisplayText":"Number of stories in house","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your house?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three or more stories","answerDisplayText":"Three or more stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1554,"questionDisplayText":"Why Gutters Need Cleaning","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need to have your gutters cleaned?  (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6871,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water isn't draining from the downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Water isn't draining from the downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6887,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water overflows from gutter and drips from joints","answerDisplayText":"Water overflows from gutter and drips from joints","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2896,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters are clogged with leaves and needles","answerDisplayText":"Gutters are clogged with leaves and needles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gutters are clogged with gravel from the roof","answerDisplayText":"Gutters are clogged with gravel from the roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":853,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"As regular maintenance to keep them working properly","answerDisplayText":"As regular maintenance to keep them working properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6871,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Water isn't draining from the downspouts","answerDisplayText":"Water isn't draining from the downspouts","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6887,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Water overflows from gutter and drips from joints","answerDisplayText":"Water overflows from gutter and drips from joints","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2896,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Gutters are clogged with leaves and needles","answerDisplayText":"Gutters are clogged with leaves and needles","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2895,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Gutters are clogged with gravel from the roof","answerDisplayText":"Gutters are clogged with gravel from the roof","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":853,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"As regular maintenance to keep them working properly","answerDisplayText":"As regular maintenance to keep them working properly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":947,"questionDisplayText":"Number of stories in house","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is your house?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three or more stories","answerDisplayText":"Three or more stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4383,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6557,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three or more stories","answerDisplayText":"Three or more stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":60001,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"Is a recurring service?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40072/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40072,"taskName":"Gutters \u0026 Downspouts - Clean","taskDescription":"Clean Gutters and Downspouts","xmTaskDescriptor":"Gutter Cleaning Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":114,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Clean Downspout Gutters Downspouts cleaning","textMessagingName":"Cln Gutter","rolloverLongDesc":"Some firms will do minor repairs at same time.","rolloverShortDesc":"Remove leaves, debris \u0026 flush out downspouts.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Clean Gutters and Downspouts.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Gutter Cleaning \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Downspout Cleaning Services","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":13,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Clean Gutters \u0026 Downspouts","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Gutters \u0026 Downspouts - Clean","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Gutter Project","urlName":"Gutters-Downspouts-Clean","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Gutter \u0026 Downspout Cleaning Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Clean, Downspout, Gutters, drain, rain, leaves","emcCategoryOid":-12014,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":394,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}